Class of 1919 Records, 1915-1997
Smith College Archives
Class of 1919 Records
1915-1997
Smith College. Class of 1919.
RG 80
19 boxes (15 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1919.
Historical Note
The Class of 1919 was the forty-first graduating class of Smith College.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Class of 1919 records contains materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1919, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, newsletters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1919 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Alumnae Council 1970 (Box 1919, Folder 1)
- Commencement 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 2)
- Commencement Address 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photographs 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 5)
- Freshman Handbook 1915 (Box 1919, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind 1915 (Box 1919, Folder 7)
- Groups 1915-1919 (Box 1919, Folder 8)
- Hoop Rolling 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 11)
- Junior Carnival 1918 (Box 1919, Folder 12)
- Class Letters ("Boojum") 1920-1960 (Box 1919, Folder 13)
- Class Letters ("Boojum") 1961-1989 (Box 1919, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous 1916-1935 (Box 1919, Folder 15)
- Organization 1915-1917, 1989-1997 (Box 1919, Folder 16)
- Phi Beta Kappa 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 17)
- Senior Dramatics 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 18)
- Senior Dramatics-Business Manager's Report 1919 (Box 1919, Folder 19)
- Class of 1919 (Box 1919.1)
- Senior Dramatics-Miscellaneous 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 1)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 2)
- Senior Dramatics-The Yellow Jacket (text) 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 3)
- Class Songs n.d. (Box 1919.1, Folder 4)
- Sophomore Reception 1917 (Box 1919.1, Folder 5)
- Step Sings 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 6)
- Class Supper 1919 (Box 1919.1, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1924 (Box 1920, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1929 (Box 1920, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 1920, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1939 (Box 1920, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1944 (Box 1920, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 1920, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 1920, Folder 7)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1920, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 1920, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 1920, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 1920, Folder 11)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 1920, Folder 12)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 1920, Folder 13)
- Reunions 1989 (Box 1920, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1994 (Box 1920, Folder 15)
- Class Secretary's Card File (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card File (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card File (Box OV)
- Reunion Memorabilia (Box OV)